https://www.sunpath.com/privacy/

Sun PathDealers910.875.9002Current Delivery Time:
18-20 weeks custom / 4-5 weeks stockProductsOur ProductsJavelin OdysseyJavelin AuroraJavelin AccuracySun Path StudentMilitaryRig Options GuideDesignerDesign Your RigMeasurement GuideCanopy CompatibilityRig Buying GuideAccessoriesShop OnlineMy AccountSupportGet SupportManualsRepairsService BulletinsProduct Improvement NoticesApproved AAD ListingFAQsCompanyAboutContactFind a DealerEmploymentLogos & MediaBlogDemo Tour Calendar
WEBSITE PRIVACY & SECURITYThis privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally Identifiable Information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect, or otherwise handle your Personal Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT FROM THE PEOPLE THAT VISIT OUR WEBSITE?When ordering or registering on our website, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other details to help you with your experience.WHEN DO WE COLLECT INFORMATION?We collect information from you when you register on our website, place an order, subscribe to a newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, register for events, or enter information on our site.How do we use your information?We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain site features. The ways we may use this information include, but are not limited to:Personalizing the user’s experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.Improving our website in order to better serve you.Allowing us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.Administration of a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.Quickly processing your transactions.Sending periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.HOW DO WE PROTECT VISITOR INFORMATION?Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible. To do this, we subscribe to SiteLock, the global leader in website security, to protect our website from hackers, spam, viruses, and scams, remove malware, and provide PCI Compliance.Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. Our website is protected by a COMODO Secure SSL Certificate to provide that secure connection.We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order, enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.Sun Path Products alsoDO WE USE ‘COOKIES’?Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site information so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.We use cookies to:Help remember and process the items in the shopping cart. Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third party services that track this information on our behalf. You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer, Chrome, or Firefox) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser’s Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.If you disable cookies, some features may be disabled on our website and may affect your experience on our website, however, you will still be able to place orders with ease.THIRD PARTY DISCLOSUREWe do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.THIRD PARTY LINKSOccasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.GOOGLEGoogle’s advertising requirements can be summed up by Google’s Advertisings Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users.https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=enWe have not enabled Google AdSense on our website but we may do so in the future.CALIFORNIA ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACTCalOPPA is the first state law in the United States to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law’s reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivable the world) that operates websites collecting personally identifiable information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this policy. – See more at http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpufAccording to CalOPPA we agree to the following:Users can visit our site anonymously Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our homepage, or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website. Our Privacy Policy link includes the word ‘Privacy’, and can be easily found on the page specified above. Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes on our Privacy Policy Page Users are able to change their personal information by either emailing us, calling us or logging into their online account.HOW DOES OUR SITE HANDLE DO NOT TRACK SIGNALS?We honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.DOES OUR SITE ALLOW THIRD PARTY BEHAVIORAL TRACKING?It’s also important to note that we do not allow third party behavioral tracking.COPPA (CHILDREN ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT)When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the United States’ consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.We DO NOT specifically market to children under 13.FAIR INFORMATION PRACTICESThe Fair Information Practices Principles from the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:We will notify the users via email within 7 business daysWe will notify the users via displaying a website notification within 7 business daysWe will also agree to the individual redress principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or a government agency to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.CAN SPAM ACTThe CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.We collect your email address in order to:Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to ordersWe may also send you additional information related to your product and/or service.Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our customers after the original transaction has occurred.To be in accordance with CANSPAM we agree to the following:We will NOT use false, or misleading subjects or email addressesWe will identify advertisement emails as such in some reasonable wayWe will include the physical address of our business or site headquartersWe will monitor third party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.We will honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quicklyWe will allow users to unsubscribe by either using a link at the bottom of the email, following instructions at the bottom of the email, or by following a process to unsubscribe as displayed on our website.CONTACTING USIf there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:Standard MailSun Path Products, Inc. 404 W. Edinborough Ave. Raeford, NC 28376 USAEmail: info@sunpath.comPhone: +1 910.875.9002QUESTIONS?If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy or the security at our web site, please contact using the information above.Copyright © 2020, Sun Path Products, Inc., All Rights Reserved.DropZone Web Design & Marketing by Beyond Marketing, LLC HomeProductsOur ProductsJavelin OdysseyJavelin AuroraJavelin AccuracySun Path StudentMilitaryRig Options GuideDesignerDesign Your RigMeasurement GuideCanopy CompatibilityRig Buying GuideAccessoriesShop OnlineMy AccountSupportGet SupportManualsRepairsService BulletinsProduct Improvement NoticesApproved AAD ListingFAQsCompanyAboutContactFind a DealerEmploymentLogos & MediaBlogDemo Tour Calendar
